https://www.cuerialawfirm.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to https://www.cuerialawfirm.com and Cueria Law Firm, LLC and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Cueria Law Firm, LLC include https://www.cuerialawfirm.com and Cueria Law Firm. The Cueria Law Firm website is a legal information and ecommerce website site. By using the Cueria Law Firm website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
In order to better provide you with products and services offered on our Site, Cueria Law Firm may collect personally identifiable information, such as your:
First and Last Name
Mailing Address
E-mail Address
Phone Number
Employer
Job Title
Cueria Law Firm may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your:
Age
Gender
We do not collect any personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. However, you may be required to provide certain personal information to us when you elect to use certain products or services available on the Site. These may include: (a) registering for an account on our Site; (b) entering a sweepstakes or contest sponsored by us or one of our partners; (c) signing up for special offers from selected third parties; (d) sending us an email message; (e) submitting your credit card or other payment information when ordering and purchasing products and services on our Site. To wit, we will use your information for, but not limited to, communicating with you in relation to services and/or products you have requested from us. We also may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.
Use of your Personal Information
Cueria Law Firm collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.
Cueria Law Firm may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Cueria Law Firm and its affiliates.
Sharing Information with Third Parties
Cueria Law Firm does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.
Cueria Law Firm may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Cueria Law Firm, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
Cueria Law Firm may disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Cueria Law Firm or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Cueria Law Firm; and/or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Cueria Law Firm, or the public.
Tracking User Behavior
Cueria Law Firm may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Cueria Law Firm, in order to determine what Cueria Law Firm services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Cueria Law Firm to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
Cueria Law Firm’s website uses advanced mouse tracking to improve the quality of content and user experience for website visitors.
Automatically Collected Information
Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Cueria Law Firm. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Cueria Law Firm website.
Use of Cookies
The Cueria Law Firm website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Cueria Law Firm pages, or register with Cueria Law Firm site or services, a cookie helps Cueria Law Firm to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Cueria Law Firm website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Cueria Law Firm features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Cueria Law Firm services or websites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
Cueria Law Firm secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Cueria Law Firm uses the following methods for this purpose:
–          SSL Protocol
When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.
We strive to take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or alteration of your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations inherent to the Internet which are beyond our control; and (b) security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Site cannot be guaranteed.
Children Under Thirteen
Cueria Law Firm does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.
E-mail Communications
From time to time, Cueria Law Firm may contact you via email for the purpose of providing announcements, promotional offers, alerts, confirmations, surveys, and/or other general communication.
If you would like to stop receiving marketing or promotional communications via email from Cueria Law Firm, you may opt out of such communications by Customers can unsubscribe from email by clicking unsubscribe.
External Data Storage Sites
We may store your data on servers provided by third party hosting vendors with whom we have contracted.
Changes to this Statement
Cueria Law Firm reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account, by placing a prominent notice on our site, and/or by updating any privacy information on this page. Your continued use of the Site and/or Services available through this Site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by that Policy.
Contact Information
Cueria Law Firm welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Cueria Law Firm has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Cueria Law Firm at:
Cueria Law Firm, LLC
700 Camp Street, Suite 316, New Orleans, Louisiana 70130
Email Address:
cuerialaw@gmail.com
Telephone number:
Office Number: 504-525-5211Address: 700 Camp St #316, New Orleans, LA 70130Google Maps   |   Get Directions
© 2020 – Cueria Law Firm, LLC
